Transliterate it also I choose to change here to Swedish.
In imported items it says that the library that imports the mail is what has created the post.
We do not change it but instead we put in
Upgraded or imported by.
Like this
So we write our library's sigel here.
So, now it's time to insert information about modifications.
You use the plus sign here to the right.
Like this
Add.
And then you choose the one at the bottom: Non-Latin characters are available in both original and translated form.
But before I leave admin metadata, I need to add another property.
Because I catalog for KB
And it is a translation of a Swedish work, I want it to be included in the Suecana collection,
And to remedy it, you would move that information to other title information.
Like this.
But that was not the case in my example.
Now we look at the release.
We see that primary publication is correct
The country is correct.
We have to transmit a place and then we enter the translite form, and it will be like this.
I cling to the place because it is not in the publication but we know that this particular publisher is from this place.
Agent, ie the publisher, we also translabs.
During the publishing tasks, the year may be repeated very many times, which may seem confusing,
But it is because the data is retrieved from different fields in the Marc21 format.
More information about this can be found in the help texts.
Our publishing details are correct so we don't change it.
To get only Swedish subject words, I end my search with SAO.
And then I get fewer hits and partly only those who are SAO meetings.
And here I have content type and it is correct, too.
And it is in English so it will be linked to Swedish when we save the post.
Now we are done with the editing and can click Create Post after a final check, here.
It remains to be posted on the mail and to see how to see the movie about stock registration.